Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
Gerard Designs Collection of Mold Drawings
- Drawings
  - #2668: 1 cavity mold 11" salad bowl, 1983; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2669: 2 cavity mold 5" salad bowl, 1983; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2672: 2 cavity mold 2100 lower housing, 1983; made for Wahconah Mold (Box 30)
  - #2673: 12 cavity mold engine and bear cookie cutter, 1983; made for Stan-Cast Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2677: 26 cavity mold 4326 centerpede parts 01-06, 1983; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 30)
  - #2680: 4 cavity mold insert two shaft collers, 1983; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 30)
  - #2682: 2 cavity mold crank knob II, 1983; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 30)
  - #2683: 8 cavity mold foam tank valve stem, 1983; made for Hope Plastics Inc. (Box 30)
  - #2684: 2 cavity mounting bracket, 1983; made for Hope Plastics Inc. (Box 31)
  - #2686: 2 cavity mold crank knob II, 1983; made for Hope Plastics Inc. (Box 31)
  - #2689: 2 cavity mold double gang decorative escutcheon, 1983; made for Nypro (Box 31)
  - #2692: 4 cavity mold RDI1 end cap, 1983; made for Nypro (Box 31)
  - #2693: 4 cavity mold PM1115 bulb retainer, 1983; made for Flowtron (Box 31)
  - #2694: 1 cavity mold GL1515 basket base, 1983; made for Flowtron (Box 31)
  - #2696: 20 cavity mold arrow, 1983; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 31)
  - #2697: 4 cavity mold RDI end cap, 1983; made for Nypro (Box 31)
  - #2698: 4 cavity mold RDI2 end cap, 1983; made for Nypro (Box 31)
  - #2699: 2 cavity mold trim plate top and bottom, 1983; made for Flowtron (Box 31)
  - #2707: 16 cavity mold dilution tube, 1983; made for Roger Tool & Die Co. (Box 31)
  - #2709: 4 cavity mold lip mirror, 1983; made for Creative Packaging (Box 31)
  - #2714: 1 cavity mold mirror bracket, 1983; made for Foster Grant (Box 31)
  - #2715: 48 cavity mold F-83 basic actuator, 1983; made for Summit Packaging Systems Inc. (Box 31)
  - #2733: 4 cavity mold fan housing, 1983; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 31)
  - #2743: 2 cavity mold cell cover, 1984; made for Hope Plastics Inc. (Box 31)
  - #2744: 2 cavity mold light stand, 1984; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 31)
  - #2746: 8 cavity mold glamour cap, 1984; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 31)
  - #2756: 20 cavity mold 4225 masts, 1984; made for Milton Bradley Co. (Box 31)
  - #2758: 4 cavity injection mold wench handle, 1984; made for Task Tool Co. (Box 31)
  - #2759: 8 cavity injection mold leg attachment, 1984; made for Task Tool Co. (Box 31)
  - #2762: 1 cavity injection mold for strap SK2317, 1984; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 32)
  - #2763: 2 cavity injection mold sleeve, 1984; made for Nypro (Box 32)
  - #2764-2765: 4 cavity injection mold nut locking ring and bushing, 1984; made for Nypro (Box 32)
  - #2767: toothbrush handle, 1984; made for Milor Inc. (Box 32)
  - #2768: 4 cavity mold for 8oz yogurt cup, 1984; made for Modern Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2769: 2 cavity injection mold PGM holder, 1984; made for Hope Plastics Inc. (Box 32)
  - #2770: 2 cavity injection mold clamp ring, 1984; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2771: 8 cavity injection mold spout, 1984; made for Thermos Division (Box 32)
  - #2775: 2 cavity injection mold 4 pin side plate, 1984; made for Task Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2779: 2 cavity injection mold strap, 1984; made for Thermos Division (Box 32)
  - #2783: 1 cavity injection mold 19 series cell cover, 1984; made for Assonett Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2784: 1 cavity injection mold 19 series case cell, 1984; made for Assonett Tool & Die Co.; also includes correspondences from small claims court filed by Gerard Designs (Box 32)
  - #2787: 2 cavity injection mold housing cover and support, 1984; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2789: 1 cavity injection mold, 1984; made for Nypro (Box 32)
  - #2790: 2 cavity injection mold extended shoe horn, 1984; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2801: 4 cavity injection mold hinged container, 1984; made for Burton Tool & Die Co. (Box 32)
  - #2803: 1 cavity injection mold molded barrel, 1984; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2807: 1 cavity injection mold battery holder, 1984; made for Digital (Box 33)
  - #2811: 4 cavity injection mold weather block cover, 1984; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 33)
  - #2815: 1 cavity mold main frame, 1984; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 33)
  - #2820: 1 cavity injection mold wheel brake, 1984; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 33)
  - #2824: 1 cavity injection mold speaker encolsure, 1984; made for Hebert Tool Co. (Box 33)
  - #2831: 1 cavity injection mold 10 lb round container, 1984; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2833: 2 cavity injection mold 3 place candle holder, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2848: 2 cavity injection mold product no. 0870 housing, 1985; made for Parker Brothers (Box 33)
  - #2849: 1 cavity injection mold halor connector, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2850: 1 cavity injection mold base power haler, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2851: 5 cavity injection mold min. computer parts, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2852: 4 cavity injection mold LED lens, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2880: 2 cavity insert loaded injection mold-red rings, 1985; made for Johnson and Johnson (Box 33)
  - #2881: 1 cavity injection mold 800 series enclosure, 1985; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 33)
  - #2942: 2 cavity mud insert for subminiature grommet, 1985; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 33)
  - #2944: single cavity mold cabinet door restraint clip, 1985; made for A. Routsis Associates (Box 33)
  - #2953: 6 cavity injection mold (2 cav cheave, 4 cav guard, 1985; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 33)
  - #2955: 1 cavity mold roller, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 33)
  - #2958: 8 cavity mold cabinet angle bracket, 1986; made for A. Routsis Associates (Box 33)
  - #2959: 2 cavity mold lockout ring, 1986; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2961: 4 cavity mold mock senser data card, 1986; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2962: 2 cavity mold secondary bobbin, 1986; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2963: 4 cavity mold escape vent, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 34)
  - #2964: 1 cavity (room for 4) threaded insert mold, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - #2971: 1 cavity mold nameplate vax pedestal, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - #2976: 4 cavity mold for covers, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 34)
  - #2979: single cavity mold 5 place candle holder, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 34)
  - #2981: 4 cavity injection mold cover, 1986; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2984: 1 cavity injection mold bottom cover, 1986; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2985, #2987: 4 cavity injection mold driver and base, 1986; made for Crisci Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2994: 8 cavity injection mold seal retainer, 1986; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2995: 8 cavity injection mold spool, 1986; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 34)
  - #2996: 4 cavity injection mold follower, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - #3001: 8 cavity injection mold valve retainer, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - #3002: 1 cavity injection mold door front, 1986; made for Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - #3003: 1 cavity injection mold platen seal brackett, 1986; made for Basque Plastics Corp. (Box 34)
  - #3004: 2 cavity injectino mold molding end cap, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 34)
  - #3006: 1 cavity injection mold door lock cam, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 34)
  - #3009: 2 cavity 8 tip strip, 1 cavity 12 tip strip, 1986; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3024: 16 cavity mold c-9 socket, 1988; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3025: 1 cavity end block cover, 1988; made for Performance Plastics East (Box 35)
  - #3026: 1 cavity mold 55405 door latch, 1988; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3027-3029: 1 and 4 cavity molds for strain relief, 1988; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3032: 4 cavity mold door stop, 1988; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3033: 4 cavity mold cuvette body, 1988; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3034: 4 cavity mold polysar test specimens, 1988; made for Vacko (Box 35)
  - #3037: 4 cavity mold areo housing, 1989; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3041: 1 cavity mold bowl cover, 1989; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3042: 2 cavity mold coin holder, 1989; made for G&S Tool & Die Co. (Box 35)
  - #3043: 6 cavity mold for curtis clip, 1989; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 35)
  - #3045-3046: 4 cavity mold 4028 melvin head and feet, 1989; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 35)
  - #3047: 1 cavity mold 4048 mickey says, 1989; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 35)
  - #3048: 2 cavity mold light cover and base, 1989; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 35)
  - #3049-3051: molds for bath seats, 1989; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3054: 1 cavity mold base for centrifuge, 1989; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3056: 1 cavity mold for front bezel, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 35)
  - #3057-3058, undated (Box 35)
  - #3099: 1 cavity injection mold ladies carry bag, 1990 (Box 36)
  - #3061: proposed change to 48 well base cover, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3066: 1 cavity injection mold coax entry panel, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3067: 1 cavity injection mold storag ebin cover, 1990 (Box 36)
  - #3068: 1 cavity injection mold transducer housing, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3069: 1 cavity mold rotor top - 12, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3075: 4 cavity injection mold vent door cover, 1990; made for F&M Tool & Die Co. (Box 36)
  - #3076: 1 1/2 cavity injection mold culture stack plate and end plate, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3077-3078: 2-8 cavity injection molds for 1 rt and 1 lt backer plate and camshaft, 1990; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3081, undated (Box 36)
  - #3082: 2 cavity injection mold bio gir test kit base and coveraft, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3083: 3 cavity injection mold bio gir test kit spreader and test strip, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3087: 4 cavity injection mold (cover) 2 handle cup, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3088-3089: 4 cavity injection mold (cover) juice cup, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3090: 4 cavity injection mold (inner cup) 2 handle cup, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 36)
  - #3091: 4 cavit yinjection mold (outer cup) juice cup, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3092: 4 cavity injection mold (outer cup) 2 handle cup, 1992; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3093: 2 cavity injection mold 6" and 11" stationary caddy, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3097: 2 cavity injection mold rt and lt lens holders, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3098-3099: 2 cavity injection mold HL123 rt and lt temple and nose pads, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3103: rieke changes FS-111, 1993; made for Plastican Inc. (Box 37)
  - #3106: 4 cavity injection mold for HL 123 nose bridges, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3109: cover container 40CSL, 1993; made for Plastican Inc. (Box 37)
  - #3110-3111: 4 cavity injection molds for bath latch and plug, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3112: 4 cavity injection mold (2 cav seat latch, 2 cav tray latch), 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3114: 4 cavity injection mold booster arm halves, 1993; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 37)
  - #3119, 3143-3145: carrying case mc 9/10; nampac 40cd cover, undated; made for Plastican Inc. (Box 37)
  - #3154: 2 cavity injectino mold horseshoe, 1996; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 38)
  - #3155: 2 cavity shoe mold, 1997; made for Anthony Tool & Die (Box 38)
  - #44BT-5: 5 1/2 gallon threaded container, undated; 2 folders; made for Plastican Inc. (Box 38)
  - Miscellaneous, 1981; 1990,; undated; 2 folders; mold drawings for Parker Brothers, Nypro, and others that are not numbered or labeled (Box 38)
Index to companies
Following is an alphabetical listing of all companies whose names appear as the client on a drawing.
A. Routsis Associates #2944 #2958
Altus Corp. #2332
Amoco Chemicals Corp. #1359 #1360
Anthony Tool & Die #2744 #2803 #2831 #2833 #2849 #2850 #2851 #2852 #2942 #2963 #2976 #2979 #3004 #3006 #3009 #3024 #3026 #3027-3029 #3032 #3033 #3037 #3041 #3049-3051 #3054 #3056 #3061 #3066 #3068 #3069 #3076 #3077-3078 #3082 #3083 #3087 #3088-3089 #3090 #3091 #3092 #3093 #3093 #3097 #3098-3099 #3106 #3110-3111 #3112 #3114 #3154 #3155
Aritech Corp. #2343
Assonett Tool & Die Co. #2783 #2784
Barry Controls #1443 #1480
Basque Plastics Corp. #3003
Bay State Plastics #1970
Beverly Pattern #1643 #1645
Bisson Bros. Tool & Die Co., Inc. #1267 #1277 #1278 #1456 #1457 #1458 #1501 #1502 #1521 #1552 #2459 #2461 #2481 #2540 #2546 #2574 #2617 #2618 #2624 #2633 #2762 #2881 #2953 #2955 #2964 #2971 #2996 #3001 #3002
Boyden Plastics #1614 #1616 #1642 #1646-1647 #1862 #1885 #2007 #2012 #2115 #2235 #2236 #2269 #2279 #2290 #2329 #2344 #2393 #2394 #2400-2401 #2407 #2440 #2451 #2463
Bradford Novelty Co. #1560 #1746
Bur-Bak Machine Corp. #1303 #1308 #2215 #2251 #2304 #2392 #2421 #2422
Burton Tool & Die Co. #1266 #1358 #1481 #1529 #1553 #1671 #1832 #2733 #2787 #2801
Byden Plastics Co.. #2160
Coleco Industries Inc. #1693 #1700 #1712 #1791 #1811 #1834 #1850 #1927 #1928 #1929 #1957 #1963 #1964 #1968 #1990 #1991 #2010 #2011 #2016 #2022 #2035 #2037 #2042 #2045 #2048 #2051 #2056 #2057 #2058 #2059 #2062
Collins Tool & Die Co. #1465 #1466 #1784 #1795 #1808 #1845
County Tool & Die Co. #2131
Creative Packaging #1841 #2213 #2709
Crisci Tool & Die Co. #1244 #1246 #1262 #1265 #1269 #1295 #1477 #1478 #1499 #1686 #1687 #1704 #1708 #1714 #1735 #1815 #1936 #1937 #1944 #2227 #2228 #2324 #2424 #2425 #2568 #2569 #2575 #2583 #2593 #2596 #2602 #2625 #2648 #2680 #2682 #2811 #2815 #2981 #2984 #2985 #2987
Crown Tool & Die Co. #1297 #1299
Danco Co. #1731
Data General Corp. #1773 #1820 #1821 #1822
Data Packaging Corp. #1279 #1280 #1283 #1305 #1337 #1471 #1500 #1634 #1635 #1699
Dee & H. Tool Co. #1547 #1548 #1549 #1550 #1622 #1758
Dejay Inc. #2512
Digital #2807
Doyle Works #1362 #1518 #1607 #1661
E. I. du Pont de Nemours #1338 #1533
E.B. Kingman Co. #1351 #1352 #1580 #1611 #1636 #1709 #1737 #2224 #2330
F&M Tool & Die Co. #2515 #2522-2523 #2558-2559 #2770 #2790 #3043 #3045-3046 #3047 #3048 #3075
Family Products #1428 #1775-1777 #1779 #1846 #1858 #1910 #1911 #1912 #1913
Flowtron #2469 #2470 #2563 #2634 #2693 #2694 #2699
Foster Grant #2714
G&S Tool & Die Co. #2959 #2961 #2962 #2994 #2995 #3042
General Electric #1948 #1949 #1950 #1951 #1952 #1953 #1954 #1955 #2080 #2080 #2597 #2598
General Electric Housewares Division #1431 #1432 #1540 #1545 #1566 #1567 #1587 #1588
Girouoard Tool & Die, Inc. #1313 #1314 #1364 #1365 #1935 #2020 #2107 #2108
Gotham Industries Inc. #1613 #1618 #1751 #2055
Hardigg Industries Inc. #1605 #1710 #1719 #1786 #2204
Hasbro Industry Inc. #1674 #1675 #1679
Hebert Tool Co. #2498 #2616 #2620 #2621 #2820 #2824
Helubel #2184
Hewlett Packard #1934 #1939
Hope Plastics Inc. #2683 #2684 #2686 #2743 #2769
ICL Inc. #2385 #2386 #2431 #2432
Improved Machinery Co. #1446 #1536
Instrumentation Laboratory Inc. #1257 #1369 #1370 #1371 #1412 #1426 #1561 #1562 #1563 #1601 #1608-1609 #2450 #2537
Iona Manufacturing Co. #1328 #1329 #1401 #1410 #1421 #1494 #1495 #1496
J&R Mold Co. #1211 #1291 #1462 #1730 #2281
Johnson and Johnson #2880
KLH #2339 #2387
L&L Mold Co. #1745 #2356
L&L Tool Co. #1786-1787 #1889 #1984
Lastomerex Inc. #1848 #1867
Lee Plastics Inc. #2638 #2640
Leominster Die & Mold Co. #1510
Leominster Die Service #1232 #1342 #1450 #1474 #1475 #1528 #1606 #1617 #1637-1640 #1732 #1733 #1755 #1796 #1814 #1824 #1827 #1839 #1920-1922 #1923 #1924 #1973 #2014 #2027 #2032 #2074 #2092 #2112 #2113 #2119 #2185 #2270 #2284 #2285 #2286 #2298 #2320 #2372 #2374 #2382 #2383 #2388 #2430 #2434 #2460 #2472 #2525 #2536 #2542 #2543 #2560 #2561 #2590
Lockwood Plastics #1941 #1942
Lockwood Products #1843
Mapco Tool #1367 #1485 #1520
Mark Technical Mold #1375 #1384 #1427 #1464 #1511 #1523 #1564 #1565 #1570 #1582 #1615 #1651 #1681 #1689 #1690 #1698
McCord #2052
Medical Polymers Inc. #2350
Milor Inc. #2767
Milton Bradley Co. #1292 #1411 #1439 #1544 #1612 #1649 #1770 #1976 #1980 #2123 #2124 #2151 #2152 #2174 #2240 #2256 #2257 #2276 #2277 #2292 #2302 #2303 #2338 #2376 #2390 #2402 #2403 #2404 #2405 #2412 #2435 #2437 #2438 #2441 #2444 #2445 #2473 #2474 #2475 #2511 #2524 #2541 #2544 #2554 #2567 #2580 #2587 #2594 #2631 #2677 #2696 #2746 #2756
Modern Tool & Die Co. #2768
Mold & Pattern Co. #1316 #1345
Monsanto #1272
Nalge #1872 #1930
Nylon Products Inc. #1932 #1933
Nypro #2054 #2076 #2502 #2689 #2692 #2697 #2698 #2763 #2764-2765 #2789 Miscellaneous
Olde Leyden Corp. #2359 #2364
Orion Research Inc. #2305 #2567
Paragon Plastics #2140
Parker Brothers #1584 #1594 #1597 #1598 #2466 #2467 #2468 #2476 #2535 #2552 #2573 #2577 #2578 #2581 #2626 #2629 #2635 #2641 #2643 #2656 #2659 #2663 #2848 Miscellaneous
Performance Plastics East #3025
Phillips MFG #1241 #1744 #1752 #1881 #1883
Plastican Inc. #3103 #3109 #3119 #3143-3145 #44BT-5
Playskool Inc. #2136 #2157
Pryde Inc. #2148
Regent Tool & Die Co., Inc. #1306 #1307
Roger Tool & Die Co. #2707
SPM Co. #1215 #1454
SRC Medical Co. #1506
Stan-Cast Inc. #1205 #1219 #1254 #1255 #1258 #1259 #1322 #1350 #1361 #1408 #1419 #1440 #1441 #1442 #1447 #1452 #1453 #1483 #1484 #1512 #1603 #1826 #2486 #2489 #2490 #2493 #2668 #2669 #2673
Sterilite Corp. #1302 #1304
Summit Packaging Systems Inc. #2715
Synthetic Products #1201 #1284 #1435 #1515 #1525 #1652 #1653 #1659 #1695 #1760 #1842 #2142 #2143 #2221
Task #2758 #2759 #2775
The Lakso Co., Inc. #1315
Thermos Division #2771 #2779
Turn Key Plastics Corp. #2200 #2201 #2202 #2211
Union Tool & Mold Co. #1317
Vacko #3034
Vertex Tool & Die Co. #2149
Victory Button Co. #1721 #1725
Wachusett Molding #1829 #1877 #1926
Wahconah Mold #2672
Westboro Plastic R&D Co. #1527